He's a relative nightmare.
Son in Law is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Steve Rash.
Country girl Rebecca has spent most of her life on a farm in South Dakota, and, when she goes away to
college in Los Angeles, Rebecca immediately feels out of place in the daunting urban setting.
She is befriended by a savvy party animal named Crawl, who
convinces the ambivalent Rebecca to stay in the city.
When Thanksgiving break rolls around, Rebecca, no longer an innocent farm girl,
invites Crawl back to South Dakota, where he pretends to be her fiancé.
Crawl, played by Pauly Shore.
Rebecca Warner, played by Carla Gugino.
Walter Warner, played by Lane Smith.
Tracy, played by Tiffani-Amber Thiessen.
Connie Warner, played by Cindy Pickett.
Walter Warner Sr., played by Mason Adams.
Son in Law is a 1993 American comedy film directed by Steve Rash, written by Fax Bahr, Adam
Small, and Shawn Schepps, and starring Pauly Shore, Lane Smith and Carla Gugino.
Although it became a box-office success, the film received mixed reviews from
critics, but because of a strong fanbase has since become a cult classic.
The film explores themes of farm, thanksgiving, college, liar, pancreas.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.